We're all just... The Sum of Us.
The Sum of Us is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Geoff Burton.
A widowed father has to deal with two complex issues: while he is searching for
"Miss Right," his son, who is in his 20s and gay, is searching for "Mr.
Harry Mitchell, played by Jack Thompson.
Jeff Mitchell, played by Russell Crowe.
Greg, played by John Polson.
Joyce Johnson, played by Deborah Kennedy.
Young Jeff, played by Joss Moroney.
Gran, played by Mitch Mathews.
The Sum of Us is a 1994 Australian LGBT-related comedy drama
film directed by Kevin Dowling and Geoff Burton.
The film is based on the 1990 play of the same name by
David Stevens, who also wrote the screenplay.
The film stars Russell Crowe and Jack Thompson.
The screen adaptation mimics the play's device of breaking the fourth wall with
direct to camera conversational asides by both Harry and Jeff Mitchell.
The film explores themes of sydney, australia, australia, based on
play or musical, breaking the fourth wall, lgbt.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.